<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Picky speaker</title>
    <link>https://neexee.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Picky speaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 11:12:50 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://neexee.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>PocketBook Quote Export</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/pocketbook-quotes/pocketbook-quotes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 05 Oct 2019 20:23:53 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/pocketbook-quotes/pocketbook-quotes/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s painful to take out quotes from PocketBook using PocketBook itself. The interface is slow and the default reader app (the best one in my opinion) has no option for bulk imports of quotes.
So I wrote a simple script to extract &amp;amp; transform quotes from the internal PocketBook DB.
The PocketBook database schema   The quote extractor You may want to change the default path of the DB, filter_quote, transform_quote and print_results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antifragile</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/antifragile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 14:26:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/antifragile/</guid>
      <description>Awesome book. It alleviated some of my scariest anxieties.
Future anxiety. Before I read it I thought I would miss something new if I&amp;rsquo;m not going to read about new shiny things every day. Turns out, new developments are not that important. People cannot solve the same problems for centuries, so it&amp;rsquo;s better to read classics to anticipate future.
Health anxiety. Health is complex. Doctors don&amp;rsquo;t know much about it and almost always create problems on the long run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 11:19:36 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/about/</guid>
      <description>  Hello! I&amp;rsquo;m Sergey. Here I write about stuff I&amp;rsquo;m genuinely interested in. It includes distributed systems, UX, GNU/Linux, teaching and self-help.
My CV   </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The beauty of typed Python</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/python-typehints/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jul 2019 11:12:50 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/python-typehints/</guid>
      <description>Here&amp;rsquo;s an example of typed Python.
import itertools from typing import Callable, Iterable, List, Tuple, TypeVar A = TypeVar(&amp;#39;A&amp;#39;) B = TypeVar(&amp;#39;B&amp;#39;) def groupby_eager(iterable: Iterable[A], key: Callable[[A], B]) -&amp;gt; List[Tuple[B, List[A]]]: groups = itertools.groupby(sorted(iterable, key=key), key=key) return [ (group_name, list(group)) for group_name, group in groups ]</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Системные вызовы UNIX</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/operating-systems-nsu/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 08 Feb 2019 10:48:58 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/operating-systems-nsu/</guid>
      <description>Что это В 2019 году я вёл курс ОС в НГУ. Это шпаргалка с примерными темами для разговора со студентами. Задачки здесь.
К сожалению, у меня не было времени написать шпаргалку для всех лаб, но примерно до десятой добралось мало студентов. И к тому времени они уже представляли, что я могу от них захотеть.
Правила
 Cпрашиваю рандомные вопросы, поэтому лучше знать все ответы знать заранее. Курсивом выделено то, что я гарантированно спрошу у каждого.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to: English</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/english/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Feb 2019 11:23:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/english/</guid>
      <description>TLDR Practice! Practice! Practice! Make a goal to study English 3+ hours per week directly and 6+ hours per week indirectly (watching videos or reading).
What matters Does matter:
 Vocabulary. 20+ thousands of words is enough. You can measure it here. Practice. Bilingual proficiency will come naturally if you&amp;rsquo;re in constant touch with the foreign language for 10+ years.  Doesn&amp;rsquo;t matter:
 Grammar. It just doesn&amp;rsquo;t stick until you start to consume almost all content in English.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Чем можно заняться первокурснику?</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/informatics-interesting/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 22 Dec 2018 11:23:41 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/informatics-interesting/</guid>
      <description>Что это? Это неформальный ответ на вопрос «У меня много лишнего времени, чем можно заняться?». Услышал я его от первокурсника.
Читать материалы курса Темы в табличку я вставлял не для того, чтобы морочить тебе голову. Любая ссылка оттуда очень интересная и полезная (если разбираться в теме не для галочки или в поисках копипасты для слайдов). В моём рассказе с первой пары тоже целая куча ссылок на качественные и интересные ресурсы.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Вопросы о параллельном программировании</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/operating-systems-multithreading/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 23 Sep 2018 10:40:02 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-ru/operating-systems-multithreading/</guid>
      <description>Что это В 2018 году я вёл практикум «Многопоточное программирование» в НГУ. Это шпаргалка с темами для разговора со студентами. Список задач
Лабораторные 1-4  Что такое поток, как он выглядит в памяти? Чем отличаются процесс и поток? Чем отличаются fork() и pthread_create()? Как ОС выделяет процессорное время для потоков и процессов? Планировщик по-разному относится к потокам и процессам? Можно ли сделать свой собственный планировщик потоков (в обход ОС)? Это где-нибудь применяется?</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>