<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>non-fiction on Picky speaker</title>
    <link>https://neexee.github.io/tags/non-fiction/</link>
    <description>Recent content in non-fiction on Picky speaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 11:24:59 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://neexee.github.io/tags/non-fiction/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>The Beginning of Infinity: Explanations That Transform the World</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/beginning-of-infinity/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Apr 2021 11:24:59 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/beginning-of-infinity/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a very wide mix of explanations about computation, biology, physics, creativity, politics, and philosophy. The explanations are pretty deep, so they explain an infinite number of phenomena. So they stand at the beginning of infinity.
The book resolved many questions for me. For example:
 What is optimism? How much a human can understand? How far we can go exploring the Universe? How to make a successful meme? Why don&amp;rsquo;t we have AI yet?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Take Smart Notes: One Simple Technique to Boost Writing, Learning and Thinking – for Students, Academics and Nonfiction Book Writers</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/smart-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 11:22:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/smart-notes/</guid>
      <description>I have mixed feelings about this book. It&amp;rsquo;s well-written on a small scale (pages, chapters) but the overall structure is a mystery to me.
Did I find a way how to organize a mess in my notes? Not exactly, but I&amp;rsquo;ve found some good hints.
Good bits:
 GTD doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for non-linear writing. Academic writing is non-linear. I was taught otherwise. Organize your notes around the context in which they&amp;rsquo;re going to be useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Surely You&#39;re Joking, Mr. Feynman!</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/joking-feynman/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 26 Jan 2020 18:36:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/joking-feynman/</guid>
      <description>If you like listen to long stories of your friends, give it a try.
I expected something different.
First of all, it shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be a book. The writing is terrible. It could not be fixed by editing because almost an entire book is based on recorded audio conversations of Feynman and his friend.
I was agonizing for the first 100 pages or so. It was too narcissistic. Maybe it&amp;rsquo;s okay, he was a kid and teenager at this time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Essential Alan Watts</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/essential-watts/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 15 Jan 2020 16:51:07 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/essential-watts/</guid>
      <description>A collection of masterpieces. Watts discusses important concepts and he goes pretty deep. Important concepts are time, Universe, God, work, ego and death. There&amp;rsquo;s no dogmatic bullshit, just a call to try to see things differently.
Sadly, I already knew most of the content from other sources. I wish I could erase my memory and read it as a completely mind-blowing book. Examples of main ideas? Past doesn&amp;rsquo;t exist. You don&amp;rsquo;t exist.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Win Friends and Influence People</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/how-to-win-friends/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Jan 2020 21:27:44 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/how-to-win-friends/</guid>
      <description>It has great overview of techniques for non-toxic conversations but it&amp;rsquo;s a little bit dangerous and shallow. I was walking around it for years and was afraid it&amp;rsquo;s a collection of insecure tricks for used car salesmans. It&amp;rsquo;s easy to read and there&amp;rsquo;s a lot of examples from lives of famous (and not-so-famous) people. So it&amp;rsquo;s a worthy read if you just want to entertain yourself.
What do I mean by dangerous?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Basic Economics: A Citizen&#39;s Guide to the Economy</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/basic-economics/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 24 Nov 2019 11:20:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/basic-economics/</guid>
      <description>Useful read. I no longer believe those who talk about things selling &amp;ldquo;below their real value&amp;rdquo; or about how terrible it is for the United States to be &amp;ldquo;a debtor nation&amp;rdquo;. I&amp;rsquo;m skeptic about government programs to make this or that &amp;ldquo;affordable&amp;rdquo;. Same skepticism goes for statements and statistics about &amp;ldquo;the rich&amp;rdquo; and &amp;ldquo;the poor&amp;rdquo;. Same with notion of &amp;ldquo;greed&amp;rdquo; of capitalists. It&amp;rsquo;s not mysterious why so many places with rent control laws also have housing shortages.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeking Wisdom: From Darwin To Munger</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/seeking-wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 21:18:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/seeking-wisdom/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a compilation of ideas from other books about thought process debugging. At least the first half. Writing is concise. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of deep quotes.
The second half was mostly about Buffet&amp;rsquo;s and Munger&amp;rsquo;s thoughts on investment bullshit so it was pretty useless.
&amp;ldquo;I read it in the New England Journal of Medicine, so it must be correct&amp;rdquo;.
Names and reputation influence us. And symbols of power or status like titles, possessions, rank, uniforms, or a nice suit and tie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Antifragile</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/antifragile/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 08 Sep 2019 14:26:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/antifragile/</guid>
      <description>Awesome book. It alleviated some of my scariest anxieties.
Future anxiety. Before I read it I thought I would miss something new if I&amp;rsquo;m not going to read about new shiny things every day. Turns out, new developments are not that important. People cannot solve the same problems for centuries, so it&amp;rsquo;s better to read classics to anticipate future.
Health anxiety. Health is complex. Doctors don&amp;rsquo;t know much about it and almost always create problems on the long run.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Visual Display of Quantitative Information</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/the-visual-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:20:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/the-visual-display/</guid>
      <description>I decided to read it because at the time of reading I had to draw a lot statistical graphs at my work and I had no idea how to do it in a best possible way. I&amp;rsquo;ve read it and convinced myself even more about facts I already knew:
 Piecharts are worthless and misleading. You need to note everything on your graph, especially axes. Your graphs shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too smart.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>