<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>★★★★★ on Picky speaker</title>
    <link>https://neexee.github.io/tags/%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ★★★★★ on Picky speaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 12:54:48 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://neexee.github.io/tags/%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Developer Hegemony: The Future of Labor</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/developer-hegemony/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 01 Dec 2019 12:54:48 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/developer-hegemony/</guid>
      <description>Totally worth your time, especially if you&amp;rsquo;re knowledge worker and you feel like grunt from time to time. I expected the book to be a little bit crazy but it isn&amp;rsquo;t. The entire corporation-driven sector of the IT industry is crazy instead.
This book is an in-depth version of Don&amp;rsquo;t Call Yourself A Programmer article, one of my favourites. And by &amp;ldquo;in-depth&amp;rdquo; I mean really deep dive into the delusion of &amp;ldquo;real programmer&amp;rdquo;.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Tangled Web: A Guide to Securing Modern Web Applications</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/the-tangled-web/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 04 Nov 2019 13:35:10 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/the-tangled-web/</guid>
      <description>Awesome book, joy to read. It&amp;rsquo;s dense, but written in a cheerful tone. The author knows a lot about web security. It&amp;rsquo;s not bound to a narrow set of technologies, frameworks, OSes or browsers. It touches a little bit of everything. But it doesn&amp;rsquo;t make it shallow. I wasn&amp;rsquo;t aware about 90% of information presented in this book. It has no cumbersome and useless terms security charlatans like. It&amp;rsquo;s very practical and full of advice.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Release it! Second edition</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/release-it/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 09 Oct 2018 14:26:47 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/release-it/</guid>
      <description>Faults and cracks:
 Fault. A condition that creates an incorrect internal state in your software. A fault may be due to a latent bug that gets triggered, or it may be due to an unchecked condition at a boundary or external interface. Error. Visibly incorrect behavior. When your trading system suddenly buys ten billion dollars of Pokemon futures, that is an error. Failure. An unresponsive system. When a system doesn’t respond, we say it has failed.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>