<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>★★★☆☆ on Picky speaker</title>
    <link>https://neexee.github.io/tags/%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%86%E2%98%86/</link>
    <description>Recent content in ★★★☆☆ on Picky speaker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 14:49:37 +0700</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://neexee.github.io/tags/%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%85%E2%98%86%E2%98%86/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Domain-Driven Design: Tackling Complexity in the Heart of Software</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/domain-driven-design/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 06 Jun 2020 14:49:37 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/domain-driven-design/</guid>
      <description>The book presents a very interesting approach to modeling complex domains, especially with established terms.
The code should look as a sentence said by a domain expert. That’s the core idea. The rest is a lengthy guide to listening to domain experts and mapping their sayings to the code.
Pros:
 Brilliant idea, totally worth knowing I could finally understand most of the content on Fowler’s blog  Cons:
 It’s very hard to follow the author.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>How to Take Smart Notes: One Simple Technique to Boost Writing, Learning and Thinking – for Students, Academics and Nonfiction Book Writers</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/smart-notes/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 18 Apr 2020 11:22:39 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/smart-notes/</guid>
      <description>I have mixed feelings about this book. It&amp;rsquo;s well-written on a small scale (pages, chapters) but the overall structure is a mystery to me.
Did I find a way how to organize a mess in my notes? Not exactly, but I&amp;rsquo;ve found some good hints.
Good bits:
 GTD doesn&amp;rsquo;t work for non-linear writing. Academic writing is non-linear. I was taught otherwise. Organize your notes around the context in which they&amp;rsquo;re going to be useful.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Seeking Wisdom: From Darwin To Munger</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/seeking-wisdom/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 03 Oct 2019 21:18:43 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/seeking-wisdom/</guid>
      <description>It&amp;rsquo;s a compilation of ideas from other books about thought process debugging. At least the first half. Writing is concise. There&amp;rsquo;s a lot of deep quotes.
The second half was mostly about Buffet&amp;rsquo;s and Munger&amp;rsquo;s thoughts on investment bullshit so it was pretty useless.
&amp;ldquo;I read it in the New England Journal of Medicine, so it must be correct&amp;rdquo;.
Names and reputation influence us. And symbols of power or status like titles, possessions, rank, uniforms, or a nice suit and tie.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>The Visual Display of Quantitative Information</title>
      <link>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/the-visual-display/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 11 Nov 2018 11:20:08 +0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://neexee.github.io/posts-en/the-visual-display/</guid>
      <description>I decided to read it because at the time of reading I had to draw a lot statistical graphs at my work and I had no idea how to do it in a best possible way. I&amp;rsquo;ve read it and convinced myself even more about facts I already knew:
 Piecharts are worthless and misleading. You need to note everything on your graph, especially axes. Your graphs shouldn&amp;rsquo;t be too smart.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>